SUSAN MOORE

https://www.susanwebdev.com | (530) 902-6086 | samoore333@gmail.com

| WEB DEVELOPER |

Web Developer with 3+ years' experience working with websites. Comfortable with working on WordPress and Wix websites for different organizations. Currently taking Full Stack Software Developer online training at Edmonds College. Recognized by prior employers for exceptional performance as an IT Specialist.

EXPERIENCE

IT Specialist, End Violence Against Women International

9/2018 to 1/2022

- Provided IT support, installed and troubleshooted software and hardware issues.
- Maintained organization websites, updating the sites, and updated content.
- Contributed other administrative duties which included managing orders, helping with correspondence to board members, filing documents in SharePoint, answering questions submitted through website and providing phone support.

Self-Employed, Susan Moore IT Services

8/2017 to 8/2019

- Provided IT support to the Colville Valley Adventist Academy which involved hardware installations and troubleshooting IT issues.
- Replaced all old computers with newer equipment which involved imaging computers and installing them on the network. Ensured servers are up and backups running.

IT Specialist, USDA-OCIO

11/2015 to 9/2016

- Installed complex, non-standard software on workstations and kept track of licensing. Provided system administration and troubleshooting support for the AS400/System 36 systems and other unique, non-CCE servers.
- Implemented and conducted inventory disposition and deployment and kept inventory database up to date.

Supervisory IT Specialist, USDA-OCIO

3/2005 to 10/2015

- Oversaw the management and performance of fifteen information technology specialists engaged in resolving and addressing the support requirements of endusers, customers, and business partners.
- Represented the SCA-IT organization on government-wide initiatives, committees, and programs pertaining to assigned program areas, services, and operations; and provided liaison and pertinent information to internal USDA and external organizations.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Business Administration, BSBA – Walla Walla University, College Place, WA

Full Stack Software Developer Online Course, Currently Completing – Edmonds College